

# **Fatemeh Baridaryan**

Front-end Developer



### about me

I have two years of experience in web programming (React-js, Next-js). Sufficient mastery of Tailwind, javaScript,Bootstrap, Html&Css, so far I have done more than 6 different projects with Next js. And I have relative familiarity with figma and ui/ux. I am very enthusiastic and committed to my work and I try to be up-to-date at least in my specialty.

## **Skils**

Next js Restful api JavaScript ES6 i18Next

React is MUI Bootstarp HTML & CSS

Redux Styled Component Tailwind css

## work experience

**- 2022 - 2023** 

**Front-end Developer** 

plof platform

**- 2021 - 2022** 

**Front-end Developer** 

**Karma Company** 

**Front-end Developer** 

**Asan Bitcoin Company** 

### **Education**

2020 - 2022

Karaj Vocational Technical

university - Computer Associate

GPA:17/51

Language

English (beginner)

Turkish

## **Projects**

baridaryan.com

https://plofmediapanel.vercel.app/

https://plof-admin-panel.vercel.app/

https://plof-cutomer-panel.vercel.app/

https://melapp.vercel.app/

https://asanbtcbot.vercel.app/